famsf.org 2017-12-22

# Privacy Policy | FAMSF

The Fine Arts Museums of San Francisco (FAMSF) is committed to protecting and respecting the privacy of our online visitors.

The FAMSF website is operated and maintained by the Corporation of the Fine Arts Museums of San Francisco, a private 501(c)(3) organization (COFAM). The terms of this privacy policy govern all online interactions with websites run by COFAM and included in the famsf.org domain, and a link to this policy is included in the footer information on every page of this website. Your use of this website constitutes your acceptance of this privacy policy.

## Collection of Information

COFAM does not collect personally identifying data, such as names, addresses, email addresses, etc., except:

  * when voluntarily submitted by website visitors
  * when making a purchase in the online FAMSF Museum Stores
  * when purchasing a membership, admission, or event tickets
  * when commenting on a FAMSF blog post
  * when sending a comment, e-postcard, or sharing an article or blog post through the page’s “forward this page” function
  * when subscribing to a FAMSF e-Newsletter

COFAM also collects information to help us learn about the number of visitors to our site and the types of technology our visitors use. We do not track or record information about individuals and their visits. We may compile and report aggregate statistics about our users—such as numbers, traffic patterns, and related site information—but these statistics include no personally identifying information.

## Disclosure of Information

COFAM will not disclose or share any personal information you provide with any other party without your permission, except if required to do so in accordance with a court order, subpoena, or similar legal order, or state or local law, and in the event such disclosure is necessary to protect the rights, property, and safety of FAMSF, its users, and other third parties.

## Links

COFAM may provide links to third party websites and other websites may provide links to the FAMSF website. Third party websites operate according to their own terms of use and privacy policies. COFAM does not monitor or control such third party websites, and therefore you acknowledge and agree that COFAM is not responsible for the availability of such third party sites, and does not endorse and is not responsible or liable for any content, advertising, products, or other materials on or available from such sites. You further acknowledge and agree that FAMSF, including the Fine Arts Museums of San Francisco, the City and County of San Francisco, the Corporation of the Fine Arts Museums, and the Fine Arts Museums Foundation, will not be responsible or liable, directly or indirectly, for any damage or loss caused or alleged to be caused by or in connection with use of or reliance on any such content, advertising, products, or other materials on or available from such sites.

## Cookies

As you browse famsf.org, advertising cookies will be placed on your computer so that we can understand what you are interested in. Our display advertising partners, including AdRoll, then enable us to present you with retargeting advertising on other sites based on your previous interaction with famsf.org. The techniques our partners employ do not collect personal information such as your name, email address, postal address or telephone number.

## Children

COFAM is committed to protecting the safety and privacy of children. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under thirteen years of age.

## Changes to this Policy

COFAM may occasionally amend this policy. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use personal information, we will announce this to site visitors via a prominent announcement on this page.

## Contact

If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy policy, our online practices, or your dealings with this website, please contact:

FAMSF Webmaster  
Corporation of the Fine Arts Museums  
de Young Museum  
50 Hagiwara Tea Garden Drive  
San Francisco, CA 94118
